Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series VIII is arranged in 6 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series VIII. RAILWAY LABOR EXECUTIVES' ASSOCIATION (R.L.E.A.)
  - Sub-Series 205-0. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - General (Featherbedding), 1963-1965 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      1963-65.
    - General (Featherbedding), 1960-1962 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      March 1, 1960-Aug. 15, 1962.
    - General (Featherbedding), 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      1959-Feb. 29, 1960.
    - General (Report of the Presidential Railroad Commission), 1961-1963 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1961-July 23, 1963.
    - General (Economic Study of Selected Railway Problems by Leon H. Keyserling), 1961-1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      1961-62.
    - General (Anti-Merger Penn-Central Railway), 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - General (Anti-Merger Penn-Central Railway), 1962-1964 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      Dec. 20, 1962-64.
    - General, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      May 1, 1964-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      Dec. 14, 1963-April 30, 1964.
    - General, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      July 1, 1963-Dec. 13, 1963.
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Aug. 16, 1962-June 30, 1963.
    - General, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      Feb. 1, 1962-Aug. 15, 1962.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      April 1, 1961-Jan. 31, 1962.
    - General, 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      Dec. 1, 1960-March 31, 1961.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Oct. 1, 1959-Nov. 30, 1960.
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Dec. 1958-Sept. 30, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 205-1. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - Assessments, 1963-1965 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1965.
    - Assessments, 1957-1962 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      1957-Dec. 31, 196246.
  - Sub-Series 205-2. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - Meetings and Material, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Jan. 17, 1961 (Washington, D.C.), Feb. 14, 1961 (Miami, Florida), March 22-24 (Washington, D.C.).
    - Minutes, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, Meetings, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, Meetings, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      May 1965.
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      March-April 1965.
    - Minutes, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Jan.-Feb. 1965.
  - Sub-Series 205-3. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - News Releases, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Jan. 10, 1963-Dec. 31, 1963.
    - News Releases, 1961-1963 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1961-Jan. 9, 1963.
    - News Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Sept. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 205-4. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - Financial Statements, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1, 1965-Dec. 31, 1965.
    - Financial Statements, 1962-1964 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      Oct. 1, 1962-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Financial Statements, 1952-1962 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      1952-Sept. 30, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 205-7. Railway Labor Executives' Association (R.L.E.A.)
    - Public Relations, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Jan. 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Public Relations, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Nov. 6, 1959-Dec. 31, 1959.